International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Records on Microfilm 5432 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 1947: Reel no.8 (Reel 177)
  - Locals-Red Rock, 1947; 1 (Reel 177)
  - Locals - Savannah, 1947; 2 (Reel 177)
  - Locals - Thunder Bay, 1947; 3 (Reel 177)
  - Int. Unions-Burns, M., 1947; 4 (Reel 177)
  - Int. Unions - Phillips, P., 1947; 5 (Reel 177)
- 1947: Reel no.9 (Reel 178)
  - Int. Unions - Smith, W., 1947; 1 (Reel 178)
  - Other Organizations, 1947; 2 (Reel 178)
  - U.S. Gov't, 1947; 3 (Reel 178)
  - Ind. Comm. - U.S. Govt., 1947; 4 (Reel 178)
  - Burka, J. P.-Gen. Files, 1947; 5 (Reel 178)
- 1947: Reel no.10 (Reel 179)
  - General Files-Conventions, 1947; 1 (Reel 179)
  - General Files-Harvard Univ., 1947; 2 (Reel 179)
  - General Files-Newspapers, 1947; 3 (Reel 179)
  - Companies - Dryden Paper Co., 1947; 4 (Reel 179)
  - Companies - Gair, R., 1947; 5 (Reel 179)
- 1947: Reel no.11 (Reel 180)
  - Companies - Garden City Paper Mills, 1947; 1 (Reel 180)
  - Companies - Powell River Co., 1947; 2 (Reel 180)
  - Companies - Company Associations, 1947; 3 (Reel 180)
- 1948: Reel no.1 (Reel 181)
  - President Secretary Files, 1948; 1 (Reel 181)
  - Officers-Killen, J., 1948; 2 (Reel 181)
  - Officers - Segal, H., 1948; 3 (Reel 181)
  - Officers - Stephens, S., 1948; 4 (Reel 181)
  - Organizers - Bell, H., 1948; 5 (Reel 181)
- 1948: Reel no.2 (Reel 182)
  - Organizers - Bever, H., 1948; 1 (Reel 182)
  - Organizers - Cook, R., 1948; 2 (Reel 182)
  - Organizers - Cagnon, W., 1948; 3 (Reel 182)
  - Organizers - Hunt, H., 1948; 4 (Reel 182)
  - Organizers - Mangan, H., 1948; 5 (Reel 182)
- 1948: Reel no.3 (Reel 183)
  - Organizers - Heinz, E., 1948; 1 (Reel 183)
  - Organizers - Trautman, W., 1948; 3 (Reel 183)
  - Organizers - Riggs, W., 1948; 2 (Reel 183)
  - Special Organizers - Moust, C., 1948; 4 (Reel 183)
  - Conference Reports, 1948; 5 (Reel 183)
- 1948: Reel no.4 (Reel 184)
  - Circular Letters, 1948; 1 (Reel 184)
  - United States-Research Dept., 1948; 2 (Reel 184)
  - Local Unions-A-Z, 1948; 3 (Reel 184)
  - Local Unions-Cohoes, 1948; 4 (Reel 184)
  - Local Unions-De Pere, 1948; 5 (Reel 184)
- 1948: Reel no.5 (Reel 185)
  - Local Unions-Detroit, 1948; 1 (Reel 185)
  - Local Unions-Caylord, 1948; 2 (Reel 185)
  - Local Unions-Iroquois Falls, 1948; 3 (Reel 185)
  - Local Unions-Los Angeles, 1948; 4 (Reel 185)
  - Local Unions - Munising, 1948; 5 (Reel 185)
- 1948: Reel no.6 (Reel 186)
  - Local Unions-Nashua, 1948; 1 (Reel 186)
  - Local Unions-Owen, 1948; 2 (Reel 186)
  - Local Unions-Savannah, 1948; 3 (Reel 186)
  - Local Unions-Sheet Harbor, 1948; 4 (Reel 186)
- 1948: Reel no.7 (Reel 187)
  - Local Unions-Shelbyville, 1948; 1 (Reel 187)
  - Local Unions-Victory, 1948; 2 (Reel 187)
  - Local Unions-Woodfibre, 1948; 3 (Reel 187)
  - General, 1948; 4 (Reel 187)
  - N.Y.S. Allied Printing Trades Council, 1948; 5 (Reel 187)
- 1948: Reel no.8 (Reel 188)
  - N. Y. S. Fed. of Labor, 1948; 1 (Reel 188)
  - Governments-United States, 1948; 2 (Reel 188)
  - Universities-General Files, 1948; 3 (Reel 188)
  - Companies, 1948; 4 (Reel 188)
  - Companies - Brompton Pulp & Paper Co., 1948; 5 (Reel 188)
- 1948: Reel no.9 (Reel 189)
  - Companies-Brown Paper Co., 1948; 1 (Reel 189)
  - Company Associations, 1948; 2 (Reel 189)
- 1949: Reel no.1 (Reel 190)
  - Officers, 1949; 1 (Reel 190)
  - Officers-Isaacson, I.D., 1949; 2 (Reel 190)
  - Officers - Richards, R.A., 1949; 3 (Reel 190)
  - Officers- Stephens, S.A., 1949; 4 (Reel 190)
  - Executive Board 1949, 5 (Reel 190)
- 1949: Reel no.2 (Reel 191)
  - Officers - Anderson, W., 1949; 1 (Reel 191)
  - Officers-Brown, P.E., 1949; 2 (Reel 191)
  - Officers-Dauer, J.E., 1949; 3 (Reel 191)
  - Officers-Hetherington, R., 1949; 4 (Reel 191)
  - Officers-Lsuman, Wm., 1949; 5 (Reel 191)
- 1949: Reel no.3 (Reel 192)
  - Officers-Leon, R., 1949; 1 (Reel 192)
  - Officers-Petretti, Joseph, 1949; 2 (Reel 192)
  - Officers-Segal, H., 1949; 3 (Reel 192)
  - Officers-Trautman, W., 1949; 4 (Reel 192)
  - Conference reports, 1949; 5 (Reel 192)
- 1949: Reel no.4 (Reel 193)
  - Circular Letters, 1949; 1 (Reel 193)
  - Local Unions--Advance, 1949; 2 (Reel 193)
  - Local Unions-Bathurst, 1949; 3 (Reel 193)
  - Local Unions-Carthage, 1949; 4 (Reel 193)
  - Local Unions-Dexter, 1949; 5 (Reel 193)
- 1949: Reel no.5 (Reel 194)
  - Local Unions-Dominion, 1949; 1 (Reel 194)
  - Local Unions-Frankford, 1949; 2 (Reel 194)
  - Local Unions-Jewell, 1949; 3 (Reel 194)
  - Local Unions - Nicolet, 1949; 4 (Reel 194)
  - Local Unions-Fort Author, 1949; 5 (Reel 194)
- 1949: Reel no.6 (Reel 195)
  - Local Unions-Port Huron, 1949; 1 (Reel 195)
  - Local Unions - Sebring, 1949; 2 (Reel 195)
  - Local Unions-Thunder Bay, 1949; 3 (Reel 195)
  - International Unions - International Brotherhood Electrical Workers, 1949; 4 (Reel 195)
  - International Unions-other Unions, 1949; 5 (Reel 195)
- 1949: Reel no.7 (Reel 196)
  - Federations- A. F. of L., 1949; 1 (Reel 196)
  - Federations-Attorneys, 1949; 2 (Reel 196)
  - Companies-Abitibi Paper Co., 1949; 3 (Reel 196)
  - Companies-Northwest Paper Co., 1949; 4 (Reel 196)
  - Companies-Swedish Pulp Employers Federation, 1949; 5 (Reel 196)
- 1949: Reel no.8 (Reel 197)
  - Treasurers' Files - Insurance, 1949; 1 (Reel 197)
- 1949: Reel no.8 (Reel 198)
  - Treasurers' Files - Insurance, 1949; 1 (Reel 198)
- 1950: Reel no.1 (Reel 199)
  - President Secretary Files, 1950; 1 (Reel 199)
  - Officers-Killen, J. S., 1950; 2 (Reel 199)
  - Officers-Segal, H., 1950; 3 (Reel 199)
  - Officer-Sherman, J., 1950; 4 (Reel 199)
  - Officers-Tonelli, J., 1950; 5 (Reel 199)
- 1950: Reel no.2 (Reel 200)
  - Executive Board, 1950; 1 (Reel 200)
  - Organizers - Brodzinski, V., 1950; 2 (Reel 200)
  - Organizers - Crawford, C.V., 1950; 3 (Reel 200)
  - Organizers - Fogelman, C., 1950; 4 (Reel 200)
  - Organizers - Grimaldi, J., 1950; 5 (Reel 200)
- 1950: Reel no.3 (Reel 201)
  - Organizers - Grogan, D.R., 1950; 1 (Reel 201)
  - Organizers- Hoff, A. B., 1950; 2 (Reel 201)
  - Organizers-Leon, R., 1950; 3 (Reel 201)
  - Organizers-Peeler, P. P., 1950; 4 (Reel 201)
  - Organizers-Ruddick, G. J., 1950; 5 (Reel 201)
- 1950: Reel no.4 (Reel 202)
  - Organizers - Shank, J., 1950; 1 (Reel 202)
  - Organizers - Van Dusen, F.C., 1950; 2 (Reel 202)
  - Organizers - Wray, M., 1950; 3 (Reel 202)
  - Circular Letters - Canadian Local Unions, 1950; 4 (Reel 202)
  - Circular Letters - United States Local Unions, 1950; 5 (Reel 202)
- 1950: Reel no.5 (Reel 203)
  - Circular Letters - West Coast Local Unions, 1950; 1 (Reel 203)
  - Local Unions - A-Z, 1950; 2 (Reel 203)
  - Local Unions-Beaver Staff, 1950; 3 (Reel 203)
  - Local Unions- Chatham Women's Auxiliary, 1950; 4 (Reel 203)
  - Local Unions - Corr. Paper Box Maker #531, 1950; 5 (Reel 203)
- 1950: Reel no.6 (Reel 204)
  - Local UnionsCorr. Paper Box Makers 535, 1950; 1 (Reel 204)
  - Local Unions-Franklin, 1950; 2 (Reel 204)
  - Local Unions-Hawkesbury, 1950; 3 (Reel 204)
  - Local Unions - Manayunk, 1950; 4 (Reel 204)
  - Local Unions-Natural Dam, 1950; 5 (Reel 204)
- 1950: Reel no.7 (Reel 205)
  - Local Unions-Nazareth, 1950; 1 (Reel 205)
  - Local Unions-Peper Bag Workers, 1950; 2 (Reel 205)
  - Local Unions - Phillips, 1950; 3 (Reel 205)
  - Local Unions-St. Regis, 1950; 4 (Reel 205)
  - Local Unions-Stevens Point, 1950; 5 (Reel 205)
- 1950: Reel no.8 (Reel 206)
  - Local Unions-Sturgeon Falls, 1950; 1 (Reel 206)
  - Local Unions-Watson Island, 1950; 2 (Reel 206)
  - Local Unione-Officer Lists, 1950; 3 (Reel 206)
  - Local Unions-Officer Lists, 1950; 4 (Reel 206)
  - Unions-Ont. & Manitoba Counsels, 1950; 5 (Reel 206)
- 1950: Reel no.9 (Reel 207)
  - Unions-Ottawa, Gatineau Councils, 1950; 1 (Reel 207)
  - Unions- A. F. of L. Rhodes, J. L, 1950; 2 (Reel 207)
  - Government-1950, 3 (Reel 207)
  - General Files, A-Z, 1950; 4 (Reel 207)
  - General Files-A-Z, 1950; 5 (Reel 207)
- 1950: Reel no.10 (Reel 208)
  - General Files - A-Z Conventions, 1950; 1 (Reel 208)
  - General Files-A-Z Conventions, 1950; 2 (Reel 208)
  - General Files-A-Z Conventions, 1950; 3 (Reel 208)
  - General Files-Journal, 1950; 4 (Reel 208)
  - General Files-Sullivan, H. N., 1950; 5 (Reel 208)
- 1950: Reel no.11 (Reel 209)
  - General Files-General, 1950; 1 (Reel 209)
  - Companies-Diamond Match Co., 1950; 2 (Reel 209)
  - Companies-Mersey Paper Co., 1950; 3 (Reel 209)
  - Companies-Utica Box Co., 1950; 4 (Reel 209)
  - Companies-Company Associations, 1950; 5 (Reel 209)
- 1951: Reel no.1 (Reel 210)
  - President Secretary Files, 1951; 1 (Reel 210)
  - Officers-Isaacson, I. D., 1951; 2 (Reel 210)
  - Officers-Richards, P., 1951; 3 (Reel 210)
  - Officers - Sherman, J., 1951; 4 (Reel 210)
  - Officers-Sherman, J., 1951; 5 (Reel 210)
- 1951: Reel no.2 (Reel 211)
  - Officers-Stephens, F., 1951; 1 (Reel 211)
  - Organizers-Aubuchon, G., 1951; 2 (Reel 211)
  - Organizers - Carney, P., 1951; 3 (Reel 211)
  - Organizers - Duretsky, H., 1951; 4 (Reel 211)
  - Organizers - Fogle, R.H., 1951; 5 (Reel 211)
- 1951: Reel no.3 (Reel 212)
  - Organizers - Fogle, R.F., 1951; 1 (Reel 212)
  - Organizer-Crogan, D., 1951; 2 (Reel 212)
  - Organizers - Harndis, A., 1951; 3 (Reel 212)
  - Organizers - Leavitt, R., 1951; 4 (Reel 212)
  - Organizers - Meinz, R.P., 1951; 5 (Reel 212)
- 1951: Reel no.4 (Reel 213)
  - Organizers - Meyer, W.S., 1951; 1 (Reel 213)
  - Organizers - Petretti, J., 1951; 2 (Reel 213)
  - Organizers - Smith, A., 1951; 3 (Reel 213)
  - Organizers - Weintz, K., 1951; 4 (Reel 213)
  - Special Organizers - Newland, L., 1951; 5 (Reel 213)
- 1951: Reel no.5 (Reel 214)
  - Special Organizers-Plaisted, J., 1951; 1 (Reel 214)
  - Organizers - Circular Letters, 1951; 2 (Reel 214)
  - Research Dept. U. S.- Brooks, G., 1951; 3 (Reel 214)
  - Local Unions-A-Z, 1951; 4 (Reel 214)
  - Local Unions-Beaver Staff, 1951; 5 (Reel 214)
- 1951: Reel no.6 (Reel 215)
  - Local Unions-Beaverwood Fibre, 1951; 1 (Reel 215)
  - Local Unions - Chicasaw, 1951; 2 (Reel 215)
  - Local Unions-Dryden, 1951; 3 (Reel 215)
  - Local Unions-Green Bay, 1951; 4 (Reel 215)
  - Local Unions-Interlake, 1951; 5 (Reel 215)
- 1951: Reel no.7 (Reel 216)
  - Local Unions-International Falls, 1951; 1 (Reel 216)
  - Local Unions-Lawrence, 1951; 2 (Reel 216)
  - Local Unions-Millinocket, 1951; 3 (Reel 216)
  - Local Unions-Palmer, 1951; 4 (Reel 216)
  - Local Unions-Philadelphia, 1951; 5 (Reel 216)
- 1951: Reel no.8 (Reel 217)
  - Local Unions-Philadelphia, 1951; 1 (Reel 217)
  - Local Unions-Richmond, 1951; 2 (Reel 217)
  - Local Unions-Seaboard, 1951; 3 (Reel 217)
  - Local Unions-Vernon, 1951; 4 (Reel 217)
  - Local Unions-Wisconsin River, 1951; 5 (Reel 217)
- 1951: Reel no.9 (Reel 218)
  - Local Unions-Wolf River, 1951; 1 (Reel 218)
  - Unions-United Mine Workers, 1951; 2 (Reel 218)
  - Federations-Ga. Fed. of Labor, 1951; 3 (Reel 218)
  - Governments- U. States N. L. R.. B., 1951; 4 (Reel 218)
- 1951: Reel no.10 (Reel 219)
  - Governments Cont.-U. States N.L.R.B., 1951; 1 (Reel 219)
  - Miscellaneous-General Files, 1951; 2 (Reel 219)
  - Companies, 1951; 3 (Reel 219)
  - Companies - Int. Paper Co., 1951; 4 (Reel 219)
  - Company Associations, 1951; 5 (Reel 219)
- 1952: Reel no.1 (Reel 220)
  - President Secretary Files, 1952; 1 (Reel 220)
  - Officers - Isaacson, I.D., 1952; 2 (Reel 220)
  - Officers-Leavitt, P., 1952; 3 (Reel 220)
  - Officers-Segal, H., 1952; 4 (Reel 220)
  - Officers-Sherman, J., 1952; 5 (Reel 220)
- 1952: Reel no.2 (Reel 221)
  - Officers-Sherman J. cont., 1952; 1 (Reel 221)
  - Organizers- Aubut, P., 1952; 2 (Reel 221)
  - Organizers-Butler, A, 1952; 3 (Reel 221)
  - Organizers-Dauer, J., 1952; 4 (Reel 221)
  - Organizers - Evans, J., 1952; 5 (Reel 221)
- 1952: Reel no.3 (Reel 222)
  - Organizers-Fogle, R., 1952; 1 (Reel 222)
  - Organizers-Green, S.., 1952; 2 (Reel 222)
  - Organizers-Kansen, H., 1952; 3 (Reel 222)
  - Organizers - Hunt, D.W., 1952; 4 (Reel 222)
  - Organizers - Meinz, E.P., 1952; 5 (Reel 222)
- 1952: Reel no.4 (Reel 223)
  - Organizers - Meyer, W.S., 1952; 1 (Reel 223)
  - Organizers - Petretti, J., 1952; 2 (Reel 223)
  - Organizers - Simone, J., 1952; 3 (Reel 223)
  - Organizers - Taylor, E.C., 1952; 4 (Reel 223)
  - Organizers - Trautman, W., 1952; 5 (Reel 223)
- 1952: Reel no.5 (Reel 224)
  - Organizers - Trinka, H., 1952; 1 (Reel 224)
  - Organizers - Wray, M., 1952; 2 (Reel 224)
  - Circular Letters - General, 1952; 3 (Reel 224)
  - Research Dept.-Canada, 1952; 4 (Reel 224)
- 1952: Reel no.6 (Reel 225)
  - Research Dept.-Brooks, G., 1952; 1 (Reel 225)
  - Local Unions-A-Z, 1952; 2 (Reel 225)
  - Local Unions-Brownsville, 1952; 3 (Reel 225)
  - Local Unions-DePere, 1952; 4 (Reel 225)
  - Local Unions-Edmundston, 1952; 5 (Reel 225)
- 1952: Reel no.7 (Reel 226)
  - Local Unions- Elizabeth, 1952; 1 (Reel 226)
  - (there isn't any), 1952; 2 (Reel 226)
  - Local Unions-Hull, 1952; 3 (Reel 226)
  - Local Unions-Menominee, 1952; 4 (Reel 226)
  - Local Unions-Norfolk, 1952; 5 (Reel 226)
- 1952: Reel no.8 (Reel 227)
  - Local Unions-Northbridge, 1952; 1 (Reel 227)
  - Local Unions-Parker Products, 1952; 2 (Reel 227)
  - Local Unions-Pulp Hill, 1952; 3 (Reel 227)
  - Local Unions-Sartell, 1952; 4 (Reel 227)
  - Local Unions-Thorold, 1952; 5 (Reel 227)
- 1952: Reel no.9 (Reel 228)
  - Local Unions-Three Rivers, 1952; 1 (Reel 228)
  - Local Unions-Wausau, 1952; 2 (Reel 228)
  - Unions-Conn. Tel. union, 1952; 3 (Reel 228)
  - Unions-Circular Letters, 1952; 4 (Reel 228)
  - Misc. Chicago, 1952; 5 (Reel 228)
- 1952: Reel no.10 (Reel 229)
  - Misc. - Labor League for Political Education, 1952; 1 (Reel 229)
  - Governments - Wage Stab. Board, 1952; 2 (Reel 229)
  - General Files-A-Z, 1952; 3 (Reel 229)
  - Companies - Diamond Match Co., 1952; 4 (Reel 229)
  - Companies-lnternational. Paper Co., 1952; 5 (Reel 229)
- 1953: Reel no.1 (Reel 230)
  - Companies-Int. Paper Co. cont., 1952; 1 (Reel 230)
  - Companies-Wilson Boxes Ltd., 1952; 2 (Reel 230)
  - Company Associations, 1952; 3 (Reel 230)
- 1953: Reel no.2 (Reel 231)
  - President Secretary Files, 1953; 1 (Reel 231)
  - Officers-Isaacson, I. D., 1953; 2 (Reel 231)
  - Officers-Richards, R., 1953; 3 (Reel 231)
  - Officers-Sherman, J., 1953; 4 (Reel 231)
  - Officers-Sherman, J., 1953; 5 (Reel 231)
- 1953: Reel no.3 (Reel 232)
  - Officers-Sherman, J., 1953; 1 (Reel 232)
  - Officers - Tonelli, J., 1953; 2 (Reel 232)
  - Organizers - Bell, H., 1953; 3 (Reel 232)
  - Organizers-Cork, F., 1953; 4 (Reel 232)
  - Organizers-Evans, J., 1953; 5 (Reel 232)
- 1953: Reel no.4 (Reel 233)
  - Organizers - Ryer, J., 1953; 1 (Reel 233)
  - Organizers - Gordon, L., 1953; 2 (Reel 233)
  - Organizers - Hansen, H., 1953; 3 (Reel 233)
  - Organizers-Howes, C., 1953; 4 (Reel 233)
  - Organizers - Lasher, H., 1953; 5 (Reel 233)
- 1953: Reel no.5 (Reel 234)
  - Organizers - Lasher, H., 1953; 1 (Reel 234)
  - Organizers-Meyer, W., 1953; 2 (Reel 234)
  - Organizers-Peeler, P., 1953; 3 (Reel 234)
  - Organizers - Smith, A., 1953; 4 (Reel 234)
  - Organizers - Smythe, P., 1953; 5 (Reel 234)
- 1953: Reel no.6 (Reel 235)
  - Organizers - Stewart, C., 1953; 1 (Reel 235)
  - Organizers - Wade, R., 1953; 2 (Reel 235)
  - Organizers - Zeininger, F., 1953; 3 (Reel 235)
  - Research and Education, 1953; 4 (Reel 235)
  - Research Dept.-Canada, 1953; 5 (Reel 235)
- 1953: Reel no.7. (Reel 236)
  - Research Dept.- Canada cont., 1953; 1 (Reel 236)
  - Research Dept.-U. S., 1953; 2 (Reel 236)
  - Local Unions- Androscoggin, 1953; 3 (Reel 236)
  - Local Unions-Chase, 1953; 4 (Reel 236)
  - Local Unions-Detroit, 1953; 5 (Reel 236)
- 1953: Reel no.8 (Reel 237)
  - Local Unions-Dexter, 1953; 1 (Reel 237)
  - Local Unions-Forest Fibre, 1953; 2 (Reel 237)
  - Local Unions-Grand Falls, 1953; 3 (Reel 237)
  - Local Unions - Kapuskasing, 1953; 4 (Reel 237)
  - Local Unions-Louisiana, 1953; 5 (Reel 237)
- 1953: Reel no.9 (Reel 238)
  - Local Onions-Lowell, 1953; 1 (Reel 238)
  - Local Unions-Norwood, 1953; 2 (Reel 238)
  - Local Unions-Paper Products, 1953; 3 (Reel 238)
  - Local Unions-Roanoke, 1953; 4 (Reel 238)
- 1953: Reel no.10 (Reel 239)
  - Local Unions-Roaring Spring, 1953; 1 (Reel 239)
  - Local Unions-Somerville, 1953; 2 (Reel 239)
  - Local Unions-Unity, 1953; 3 (Reel 239)
  - Local Unions-Woodland, 1953; 4 (Reel 239)
  - Paper Makers - Daggett, R., 1953; 5 (Reel 239)
- 1953: Reel no.11. (Reel 240)
  - Paper Makers -Fisher, M., 1953; 1 (Reel 240)
  - A. F. of L.-O'Reilly, H., 1953; 2 (Reel 240)
  - Other Organizations-Int. Labor Press, 1953; 3 (Reel 240)
  - U. S. Govt.-National Labor Relations Board, 1953; 4 (Reel 240)
  - General Files-Colleges, 1953; 5 (Reel 240)
- 1953: Reel no.12 (Reel 241)
  - General Files-Convention, 1953; 1 (Reel 241)
  - General Files-Credentials, 1953; 2 (Reel 241)
  - General Files-Credentials cont., 1953; 3 (Reel 241)
  - General Files-Convention Material, 1953; 4 (Reel 241)
  - General Files - Hook, A., 1953; 5 (Reel 241)
- 1953: Reel no.13 (Reel 242)
  - General Files-Journal Pictures, 1953; 1 (Reel 242)
  - General Files - General, 1953; 2 (Reel 242)
  - Companies - Ohio Boxboard Co., 1953; 3 (Reel 242)
  - Company Associations, 1953; 4 (Reel 242)
- 1954: Reel no.1 (Reel 243)
  - President Secretary Files, 1954; 1 (Reel 243)
  - Officers-Isaacson, I., 1954; 2 (Reel 243)
  - Officers-Richards, R., 1954; 3 (Reel 243)
  - Officers - Sherman, J., 1954; 4 (Reel 243)
  - Officers -Sherman, J., 1954; 5 (Reel 243)
- 1954: Reel no.2 (Reel 244)
  - Officers-Stephens, 1954; 1 (Reel 244)
  - Organizers - Bell, H., 1954; 2 (Reel 244)
  - Organizers - Candamedo, J., 1954; 3 (Reel 244)
  - Organizers - Dubetsky, H., 1954; 4 (Reel 244)
  - Organizers-Gagnon, W., 1954; 5 (Reel 244)
- 1954: Reel no.3 (Reel 245)
  - Organizers-Gear, C., 1954; 1 (Reel 245)
  - Organizers-Hansen, H, 1954; 2 (Reel 245)
  - Organizers-Harnois, A., 1954; 3 (Reel 245)
  - Organizers-Leon, R., 1954; 4 (Reel 245)
  - Organizers-Minota, Z., 1954; 5 (Reel 245)
- 1954: Reel no.4 (Reel 246)
  - Organizers-Mobley, A., 1954; 1 (Reel 246)
  - Organizers-Price, L., 1954; 2 (Reel 246)
  - Organizers-Simone, J., 1954; 3 (Reel 246)
  - Organizers-Taylor, E., 1954; 4 (Reel 246)
  - Organizers-Van Deusen, F., 1954; 5 (Reel 246)
- 1954: Reel no.5 (Reel 247)
  - Organizers-Wade, R., 1954; 1 (Reel 247)
  - Organizers-Zeininger, E., 1954; 2 (Reel 247)
  - Circular Letters, 1954; 3 (Reel 247)
  - Research Dept.-Brooks, G., 1954; 4 (Reel 247)
  - Research Dept.-Brooks, G, 1954; 5 (Reel 247)
- 1954: Reel no.6 (Reel 248)
  - Research Dept.-Brooks, G., 1954; 1 (Reel 248)
  - Local Unions-Appleton, 1954; 2 (Reel 248)
  - LocaI Unions-Central, 1954; 3 (Reel 248)
  - Local Unions-Dryden, 1954; 4 (Reel 248)
  - Local Unions-Fibre & Plastic Workers, 1954; 5 (Reel 248)
- 1954: Reel no.7 (Reel 249)
  - Local Unions-Fitzdale, 1954; 1 (Reel 249)
  - Local Unions-Green Bay, 1954; 2 (Reel 249)
  - Local Unions- Livermore Falls, 1954; 3 (Reel 249)
  - Local Unions-Munising, 1954; 4 (Reel 249)
  - Local Unions-Northern, 1954; 5 (Reel 249)
- 1954: Reel no.8 (Reel 250)
  - Local Unions-Norwood, 1954; 1 (Reel 250)
  - Local Unions-Panama City, 1954; 2 (Reel 250)
  - Local Unions-Port Alberni, 1954; 3 (Reel 250)
  - Local Unions-Sartell, 1954; 4 (Reel 250)
  - Local Unions-United Brotherhood, 1954; 5 (Reel 250)
- 1954: Reel no.9 (Reel 251)
  - Local Unions-U. S. Corrug. Workers, 1954; 1 (Reel 251)
  - International Unions, 1954; 2 (Reel 251)
  - Unions-Jones, J. R., 1954; 3 (Reel 251)
  - Misc. - Labors League for Political Education, 1954; 4 (Reel 251)
  - Govt. - United States, 1954; 5 (Reel 251)
- 1954: Reel no.10 (Reel 252)
  - Govt.-United States N.L.R.B., 1954; 1 (Reel 252)
  - General Files-A-Z, 1954; 2 (Reel 252)
  - Companies, 1954; 3 (Reel 252)
  - Companies - Pacific Mills Ltd., 1954; 4 (Reel 252)
  - Company Associations, 1954; 5 (Reel 252)
- 1955: Reel no.1 (Reel 253)
  - President Secretary Files, 1955; 1 (Reel 253)
  - Officers - Isaacson, I., 1955; 2 (Reel 253)
  - Officers-Lorrain, L., 1955; 3 (Reel 253)
  - Officers-Segal, H., 1955; 4 (Reel 253)
  - Officers-Sherman, J., 1955; 5 (Reel 253)
- 1955: Reel no.2 (Reel 254)
  - Officers-Stephens, S., 1955; 1 (Reel 254)
  - Executive Board, 1955; 2 (Reel 254)
  - Organizers - Avanzato, T., 1955; 3 (Reel 254)
  - Organizers-Carney, P., 1955; 4 (Reel 254)
  - Organizers-Evans, J., 1955; 5 (Reel 254)
- 1955: Reel no.3 (Reel 255)
  - Organizers-Ryer, J., 1955; 1 (Reel 255)
  - Organizers-Green, S, 1955; 2 (Reel 255)
  - Organizers-Hetherington, P., 1955; 3 (Reel 255)
  - Organizers - Jamison, W., 1955; 4 (Reel 255)
  - Organizers-Lyons, J., 1955; 5 (Reel 255)
- 1955: Reel no.4 (Reel 256)
  - Organizers - Mangan, E., 1955; 1 (Reel 256)
  - Organizers-Patin, A., 1955; 2 (Reel 256)
  - Organizers-Share, C., 1955; 3 (Reel 256)
  - Organizers-Stewart, C., 1955; 4 (Reel 256)
  - Organizers-Taylor, R., 1955; 5 (Reel 256)
- 1955: Reel no.5 (Reel 257)
  - Organizers - Trautman, W., 1955; 1 (Reel 257)
  - Organizers - White, P., 1955; 2 (Reel 257)
  - Misc. Wage Negotiations, 1955; 3 (Reel 257)
  - Misc. Circulars, 1955; 4 (Reel 257)
  - Research Dept. of Canada, 1955; 5 (Reel 257)
- 1955: Reel no.6 (Reel 258)
  - Research Dept. - United States, 1955; 1 (Reel 258)
  - Locals-A-Z, 1955; 2 (Reel 258)
  - Locals-Blackwater, 1955; 3 (Reel 258)
  - Locals-Cincinnati, 1955; 4 (Reel 258)
  - Locals-Eastport, 1955; 5 (Reel 258)
- 1955: Reel no.7 (Reel 259)
  - Locals-East Ryegate, 1955; 1 (Reel 259)
  - Locals-Garden City, 1955; 2 (Reel 259)
  - Locals-Jersey, 1955; 3 (Reel 259)
  - Locals- Marion, 1955; 4 (Reel 259)
  - Locals-Neenah, 1955; 5 (Reel 259)
- 1955: Reel no.8 (Reel 260)
  - Locals- Nekoosa-Edwards, 1955; 1 (Reel 260)
  - Locals-Owen, 1955; 2 (Reel 260)
  - Locals - Port Huron, 1955; 3 (Reel 260)
  - Locals - Salem, 1955; 4 (Reel 260)
  - Locals - Terrace Bay, 1955; 5 (Reel 260)
- 1955: Reel no.9 (Reel 261)
  - Locals - Texas, 1955; 1 (Reel 261)
  - Locals - Waco, 1955; 2 (Reel 261)
  - International Unions, 1955; 3 (Reel 261)
  - Unions - Research Dept., 1955; 4 (Reel 261)
  - Unions - A.F. of L. Circulars, 1955; 5 (Reel 261)
- 1955: Reel no.10 (Reel 262)
  - Unions - Conventions, 1955; 1 (Reel 262)
  - Unions - Federations, 1955; 2 (Reel 262)
  - Governments - U.S. N.L.R.B, 1955; 3 (Reel 262)
  - General Files, A-Z, 1955; 4 (Reel 262)
  - General Files - Misc. A-Z, 1955; 5 (Reel 262)
- 1955: Reel no.11 (Reel 263)
  - Companies, 1955; 1 (Reel 263)
  - Companies-International Paper Co., 1955; 2 (Reel 263)
  - Company Associations, 1955; 3 (Reel 263)
- 1956: Reel no.1 (Reel 264)
  - President Secretary Files, 1956; 1 (Reel 264)
  - Officers-Isaacson, I, 1956; 2 (Reel 264)
  - Officers-Lorrain, L, 1956; 3 (Reel 264)
  - Officers-Segal, H., 1956; 4 (Reel 264)
  - Officers-Sherman, J., 1956; 5 (Reel 264)
- 1956: Reel no.2 (Reel 265)
  - Officers-Stephens, S., 1956; 1 (Reel 265)
  - Organizers - Anderson, W., 1956; 2 (Reel 265)
  - Organizers - Bell, H., 1956; 3 (Reel 265)
  - Organizers-Cook, G., 1956; 4 (Reel 265)
  - Organizers - Derhammer, R., 1956; 5 (Reel 265)
- 1956: Reel no.3 (Reel 266)
  - Organizers-Detreville, W., 1956; 1 (Reel 266)
  - Organizers-Gordon, L., 1956; 2 (Reel 266)
  - Organizers-Hsnsen, H., 1956; 3 (Reel 266)
  - Organizers-Hopkins, F., 1956; 4 (Reel 266)
  - Organizers - LaRoche, J., 1956; 5 (Reel 266)
- 1956: Reel no.4 (Reel 267)
  - Organizers-Lasher, H., 1956; 1 (Reel 267)
  - Organizers-Minota, T., 1956; 2 (Reel 267)
  - Organizers-Price, L., 1956; 3 (Reel 267)
  - Organizers-Steele, R., 1956; 4 (Reel 267)
  - Organizers-Stone, J., 1956; 5 (Reel 267)
- 1956: Reel no.5 (Reel 268)
  - Organizers-Taylor, T., 1956; 1 (Reel 268)
  - Organizers-Wentz, K., 1956; 2 (Reel 268)
  - Organizers - Derrickson, G., 1956; 3 (Reel 268)
  - Misc.-Circular Letters, 1956; 4 (Reel 268)
  - Research & Education Dept., 1956; 5 (Reel 268)
- 1956: Reel no.6 (Reel 269)
  - Research Dept. of Canada, 1956; 1 (Reel 269)
  - LocaIs-A-Z, 1956; 2 (Reel 269)